why did you climb into the Kursk
а что ты полез оккупант в курскую
region, you, the occupier, climb into the
область это вы оккупант полезли в
Kursk region, we came to you, so to the
курскую область мы к вам на так на
Kursk region, we didn’t touch your peaceful cities,
Курская область мы ваши мирные города не
what, wait, why did you climb into the Kursk
трогали ели что подожди что вы полезли в
region, you should have been sitting in
курскую область надо было сидеть в
Ryazan? Why did you climb into the Kursk region to
Рязани Зачем ты полез в курскую область
fight, Motherland
воевать мать Родина
forced you, oh, another one who’s sitting, let’s have a normal conversation, he’s
заставила о ещё один какой сидит давай
filming videos, no, let’s have a normal
ролики снимает на Нет давай нормально
conversation,
пообщаемся
let’s have a normal conversation,
давай нормально пообщаемся
let’s I’m Russia,
давай я Россия
Ryazan, my dad was in the Airborne Forces, he served in a school there, he
Рязань у меня батя ВДВ там в училище
studied, like, in Ryazan. Well, why are
служил учился типа в Рязани Ну а почему
you so real now? I’m generally
ты сейчас такой истинный Я вообще
Lithuanian. I’m in Lithuania. Well,
литовец Я в
just write to Lithuania, Ukraine,
Литве Ну Литве просто напи Украину тебя
I didn’t put any VN on you. I don’t know what it is, I put it.
я никакие VN не ставил Я не знаю что это
And I’m Russian, I don’t know the
та я поставил А я русский я не знаю виу
police, I can see from your face that you’re
полиц я вижу по лицу что ты
Russian. So what are you going to tell me? What do you
русский Ну и что ты мне расскажешь Кем
do at the moment? Nobody at
работаешь на данный момент никем на
the moment. On
данный момент На
crutches, happened. What
костылях случилось Что
happened. Well, a little bit, your. Drone,
случилось Ну немножко мне ваши Дрон
podra  Neli Where In what
подра Нели А где На каком
direction is normal direction on
направлении нормально направление на
Kursk on Kursk And why did you climb
Курском на Курском А что ты полез
into the Kursk
оккупант в курскую
region, occupier, it is you, occupier, who climbed into the Kursk region,
область это вы оккупанта полезли в
we are to you, so on Kursk region, we did
курскую область мы к вам на так на
not touch your peaceful cities,
Курская область мы ваши мирные города не
wait, why did you climb into the Kursk
трогали подожди что вы полезли в курскую
region, you should have stayed in Ryazan Why did you
область надо было сидеть в Рязане Зачем
climb into the Kursk region to
ты полез в курскую область
fight, mother Motherland forced you What is
воевать мать Родина заставила Какая
your homeland, your homeland, Ryazan, why did you climb into Kursk
родина твоя родина Рязань что ты в Курск
This is Ukraine Kursk
полез Это Украина Курская
region, this is Ukraine Kursk
область это Украину курскую
region, I explain Kiev prince Vladimir
область объясняю Киевский князь Владимир
founded the city of
основал город
Kursk And this is the Kiev prince himself, Russia,
Курск А это сам Киевский князь России же
he
он
was not there and Russia did not exist then Moscow did not
был не было и России не было тогда
even exist Moscow then, by the way,
Москвы даже не было Москву потом кстати
Moscow is also here,
Москву тоже сде
man, don’t look at what you are sitting there
мужик вот не гляди то что ты сидишь там
filming on only or where are you filming,
снимаешь на только или куда снимаешь
explain Why did you, for what money, go to
объясни Зачем ты Ты что за деньги пошёл
fight in the Kursk region in a foreign country,
воевать в курскую область в чужую страну
yes, a foreign country, all your life was Kursk
да чужая страна всю жизнь был Был Курск
Russia, I am a country of cut all this is no longer
Россия я страна реза всё это уже не
Russia, it is already
Россия это уже
Ukraine since the years Ukraine because Ukraine
Украина с лет Украина потому что Украина
we are we  proclaimed Well, yes, tell me what it is,
мы мы провозгласили Ну да кажи что это
why did the referendum grow,
почему рос
half of Ukraine Crimea is Ukraine
полу Укра Крым это Украина
occupied by the Russian Federation, and the
оккупированный Российской Федерацией а
Kursk region is Ukraine, this is itself How
Курская область это Украина это само Как
else can I say this,
ещё сказать это
KhRU, how can I
хру как же
say it, too, Russia, tell me, it turns out that
сказать тоже росия скажи получается вот
you received payments for the
ты получил выплаты за
wounds, how much did you receive,
ранени получил сколько
Milne, so it seems like they give three rubles Well, they used to give three
Милн так вроде трёшку дают Ну это раньше
rubles only when the contract included
трёшку только когда контракт включил уже
five rubles, I understood, and before the contract What did you
пятёрку дают понял а до контракта Кем
work for, honestly? To be honest, I
работал честно Вот честно
worked for a long time, I understood And what did you go and
работал понял А что пошёл бабки
earn money for a contract? No, I went to
заработать на конт Нет я пошёл своих
protect my children so that people like you,
детей защитить чтоб такие как вы
occupiers, would not come to our country,
оккупанты не пришли к нам в страну
wait So why is Ryazan there, we are taking back
подожди Так зачем там Рязань мы забираем
our Kursk region Why do we not
свою курскую область Зачем нам Рязань не
need Ryazan, our Kursk region? Vyra What is
нужна свою курскую область Выра Какая
your Kursk region, we have already
ваша Курская область мы у вас уже
taken half the country from you? Look, according to the
полстраны отобрали Посмотри по
Munich Agreement of 1917, yes,
во мюнхенскому договору 1917 года да
Moscow recognized the Kursk region for
Москва признавала курскую область за
Kiev, that's all, tell me, so what's all?
Киевом всё сжи скажи мне ещ так что всё
You are an occupier, you went to seize the Kursk region, I
Ты оккупант ты пошёл курскую область
don't know what
захватывать что таких слов не знаю что
else, so what is Kursk  the region there people are
ещё так что Курская область там люди
Ukrainian speaking there everyone speaks Ukrainian
украиноязычный там все по-украински
These are Ukrainian original
говорят Это украинские исконные
territories in Sochi they also speak
территории в Сочах тоже говорят
Ukrainian
по-украински
Sochi is also Ukrainian Yes Ukraine is
Сочи тоже украинская Да Украина
Georgian half
грузинская половина
y And why do they all have
у А почему же они там на у них всех
Russian passports there because
русские паспорта та потому что
occupied Russia gave them
оккупированная Россия раздала им
passports like that there
паспорта такой там
guys look in Germany there are also people with
мужи смотри в Германии тоже есть люди с
Russian passports and what is this Russia
русскими паспортами и что это Россия
now in Germany there are no people with Russian
теперь в Германии нету людей с русскими
passports there is dual citizenship
паспортами там есть двойное гражданство
Listen here is a question for you as a
Слушай а вот такой вопрос тебе как
military man I just don't know why
военному Я просто не шарю в этом почему
Putin instead of throwing
Путин вместо того чтобы скинуть на Киев
some nutcracker on Kyiv and ending the war
какой-то орешник и закончить войну
throws guys like you to
бросает Вот таких как ты пацанов
die because Putin is a good
умирать потому что Путин правильный
man he is not like you Zelensky
мужик он не такий Как у вас Зеленский
throws you expired on civilians if Putin wanted We would have already poured your
кидает если Путин хотел Мы бы уже вашу
Ukraine in days of the Armed Forces
Украину за дня ВС проли
because he pities your children and you
во потому что он ваших детей и вас
but does not pity you it turns out that he does
жалеет а вас не жалеет получается то
not pity you he
есть тебя не жалеет нас
pities us of course he pities yours
жалеет конечно жалеет он ваших детей
pities children and grandfathers and grandmothers he would have
жалеет и дедок и бабушек он бы сейчас
thrown 25 now yes at least five fighters
кинул 25 да хотя бы пять истребителей
flew your country in half a day they would have passed
полетело вашу краину за полдня прошли бы
so they would have passed in half a day end the war
так прошли бы за полдня война закончи
Why 3 years of
Зачем 3 года
nonsense Well I don't know why he is muting yes Well here he is I
муть Ну не знаю зачем он мут да Ну вот
say he he pities your children
он я говорю он он ваших детей жалеет
your civic residents so look just put a stop to the
ваших ных жителей так смотри просто на
Verkhovna Rada because he pities the fascists
верховную Раду нанули бо фашистов жалеет
right Well look look at the
правильно Ну смотри смотри по центрам
decision-making centers did not strike once
принятия решения не ударил один раз один
once on Kyiv for the sake of the hazelnut and that's
раз по Киеву поради орешника и
it Well they got it anyway no no And
всё Ну получили же всё равно не не А
if on the 22nd the enemy
если тебе 22 реник
flies what will
прилетит что там
remain of Kiev the raven There will be a raven
Киевом останется ворон Остане ворон
win and you suffer only boys
победите а же Вы мучаетесь лько пацанов
like you wounded now the dead are lying here
как ты раненные теперь убитые лежат вот
you are lying now so if Putin had
ты сейчас лежишь так бы Путин один
pressed one hazelnut you would have already made a parade on Red
орешник нажал вы бы уже парад на Красной
Square and that's it ladies we will soon
Площади сделали и всё дамы парад скоро
make a parade in the center of
сделаем в центре
Kyiv
Киева парад
your parade we don't want to seize it
ваш не хотим мы его захватывать тебе
anymore I will tell you right So you have already
больше скажу правильно Так вы же уже
been near
были под
Kiev Yes you have  it's just that
Киевом Да были это вот просто вот
Vladimir Vladimirovich my beloved
Владимир Владимирович мой любимый
president gave the go-ahead And it would have been a
президент дал отмашку А так бы уже
long time ago that he gave
давно что он такой дал
the go-ahead Well, he didn't want to kill
отмашку Ну он не захотел убивать мирных
civilians He's just not like
жителей Просто он не такой же как
you old grannies in a dungeon
вы бабушек стареньких в подземелье
drive them there Torba or whatever you
загоняй там их Торба или что там вы
do I don't know yeah yeah so look why I would have
делаете Я не знаю да да так смотри зачем
just run into Kyiv to
вот просто забежал бы в Киев в дворец
Zelensky's palace arrest Zelensky all the
Зеленского арестовал Зеленского всё
special forces and by helicopter No, it's not you we
спецназ и на вертолёте Да не вам нам ваш
need your Zelensky we don't need him Oh he would have
Зеленский нужен он нам не нужен О он бы
signed the capitulation That's how he would have looked take
подписал капиту Вот так он бы смотри
him they would have brought him to Moscow to the
взял бы его привезли бы его в Москву в
Kremlin he would have signed the
Кремль он подписал бы
capitulation yes we need you
капитуляцию да нам нужен вас
expired Zelensky Tell me
просроченный Зеленский Вот скажи
please Well who should sign the
пожалуйста Ну а кто должен подписать
capitulation VV Putin Well,
капитуляцию ВВ Путин Не ну со стороны
who should sign on the part of Ukraine that Ukraine
Украины кто должен подписать что Украина
surrenders Oh yeah the country of Ukraine there is no
сдаётся Ой да страны Украины Украины
such country anymore Well,
такой больше страны нету уже Да ну
someone should sign the capitulation you've been in
кто-то должен подписать капитуляцию вы
debt to America for 100 years what Ukraine What are you
уже 100 лет должны Америке какая Украина
talking about
О чём говори
488 What are you talking about What Ukraine
488 О чём ты говоришь Какая Украина то
no  such a bigger country So we we are the
нет такой больше страны Так мы мы штат
fifty-first state of America
Америки пятьдесят первый
Yes by level What month are we in
Да по уров На каком меся стоите мы п
America your place by IQ level And
Америки сеье место у вас по уров IQ А
what is
что такое
IQ by the level of
IQ по уровне
stupidity Well how to decipher IQ Well IQ
глупости Ну как расшифровывать IQ Ну IQ
level of the stupid population Well well
уровень глупого населения
this is in English and so the level of the
Ну ну это по-английски а так уровень
stupid population I tell you in Russian
глупого населения тебе по-русски
and what is the slope of this coefficient
говорю и что покат этот коэффициент
Tell me smart person Well this is
Расскажи мне умный человек Ну вот это
your place You are the stupidest
Вот ваше во сеье место Вы самые глупые
Of all the countries And how many countries are the first the
Изо всех стран А сколько всего стра самы
very first Japan so and
первы самая первая Япония так а
Russia Russia is in sixth place
Россия Россия на шестом месте
so that is that is you are a representative of a
так то есть то есть ты представитель
nation that is in the top ten
нации которая в первую десятку по уровню
in the world by IQ level Yes yes of course you
IQ входит в мире Да да конечно ты
consider yourself a smart person with a
считаешь себя умным человеком с
big I am not a
большим Я не
smart mind I have long since covered your whole country with a
умный ум я уже давно вашу страну всю
copper basin Listen Wait how is it
накрыл медным тазом Слушай Подожди как
correctly written in Russian stupid or
правильно пишется в русской глупой или
Stupid stupid probably good if you are
Глупый глупый наверное хорошо если ты
stupid how did you understand that Ukraine is in such a
глупый как ты понял что Украина на таком
place by IQ Well you go to Wikipedia Go and
месте по IQ Ну ты в Википедию Зайди и
ask in order to something in order to
спроси для того чтобы что-то для того
read some  Wikipedia Yes, you
чтобы прочитать какую-то Википедию Да
need to realize, understand, pass through
нужно осознать понять пропустить через
yourself, that is, the thought
себя то есть мыслительный
process Yes, you even have a flag Did you
процесс да у вас даже флаг нь Вы что в
drown in the
море утонули в
sand at sea? You are saying this now as a
песке Это ты говоришь сейчас как
representative of a country with a high IQ
представитель страны с большим IQ
Yes, of course, I have the highest
Да конечно у меня самый большой
IQ How many centimeters is your
IQ Сколько сантиметров у тебя
IQ Should I show you how many IQs there are,
IQ тебе показать сколько сонме IQ да
show me
покажи
[music]
[музыка]
Well, I'm afraid it won't fit in your mouth Well, tell me Show me
Ну боюсь те в рот не влезет Ну скажи
how many centimeters are
Покажи сколько сантиметров
yours What do you praise in the tube with your
твой что В тубе вы хвали своим
dignity I know you're
достоинством я знаю
taking off in the world, sixth place in the world Show the
снима в мире шестое место в мире Покажи
whole world
всему миру
yours You're hiding such a
сво ты прячешь такое
treasure of dates I'm afraid
достояние даты пови боюсь
honestly six
честно шесть
unfinished by
незаконченных по
level by level like
уровню по уровню как
five Well, it seems like your frog also has
пять Ну вроде вроде тоже у лягушки твоей
sideburns What are you twitching about Yes, I should get up a little It's
дёргаешься Да я привстать немножко мне
hard for me to pester you I understood And what's wrong with your
же тяжело приставать понял А что у тебя
IQ, why are you like that IQ Yes, mine
IQ привстал что ты так IQ Да у меня
got up like
привстал
that Listen, how is it that you
такую Слушай а как вот получается что ты
went to war And now You'll be without two legs
пошёл на войну А теперь Без двух ног
Repeat again how is it that you went
повтори как так получается что ты пошёл
to war And now you'll be without
на войну И теперь будешь без
legs Why are you without legs  me
ног Почему без ног у меня
now in May my
сейчас в мае месяце закончится мой
maternity leave will end Kolya and I will go back
декретный отпуск Колян и я пойду назад
your maternity leave you got
ваших декретный ты это
pregnant I have
забеременел я ваших там
a little of yours there listen men can also
немножко слушай мужики же тоже могут
go on maternity leave it is not
декрет в декрет отку ходить не
necessary to go on maternity leave a woman do you have a wife
обязательно бабя есть у тебя есть жена
children I had a wife three children I
дети была у меня жена трое детей у меня
have and my wife was three children I have
есть а жена была трое детей есть у меня
and what about my wife
а что с женой
now Yes I am with her who is she
сейчас Да я с ней кто её там
maybe I don't know And children where I definitely have
может не знаю А дети де у меня точно
children you
есть детей
see Every day they go to school from me
видишь Каждый день они от меня в школу
by bus to school Well
ходят на автобусе ет в школу Ну живут
they live there with her Well this is the same they come to me
они там у неё Ну это самое они ко мне
every day you help with
приезжают каждый день помогаешь
money there is not that much money How much do
деньгами денег столько нет Сколько у
they have And who
них А кто у них
earns money for them And who earns money for them for now they
зарабатывает А кто у них зарабатывает
pay me for the injury on
мне вот пока за ранение платят по
sick leave all the money is theirs And you
больничному все деньги ихние А ты им
give them the money Yes and
отдаёшь деньги
why do I need them Maca drives me
Да а они мне зачем нужны Мака мне
vodka Listen and if you for the DHT
горилку гонит Слушай а если тебя за дхт
how much will they pay your
сколько выплатят
wife 12 million maybe you know better why with
жене 12 лямов може лучше знаешь зачем
injuries ba at once 12 million and
ранениями ба сразу 12 лямов и
invest Well come on you maybe those
инвестируй Ну давай тебя может те
will pay there la I don't mean there take it
заплатит там ля не име в виду там возьми
right away in a fight somewhere there and everything would
сразу в бою где-то там и всё бы
work out shi
получится ши
Ukrainians don't pay for suicide bombing for
украинцы за самоподрыв не
years
выплачивают года
not to mention you for your
не то что вы за своего
Zelensky And what did Putin do to you that
Зеленского А что тебе сделал Путин что
you want to die for him
ты хочешь за него
he did Well for example
умереть он сделал Ну например
Well for example firstly amnesty zone And you
Ну например во-первых зона амнисти А ты
were in the zone he amnesty you Therefore are you
сидел на зоне он тебя амнисти Поэтому ты
ready to die for him in what year he
за него готов умереть в каком году он
amnesty you
тебя амнисти
in 2020 trip not
в 2020 трип не
seriously Well seriously In 2022 2m yes And
серьёзно Ну серьёзно В 2022 2м да А за
what did you
что ты
sit for Well for someone like you yes seriously
сидел Ну за такого как ты да серьёзно
sat there murder robbery what Well I'm telling you
сидел там убийство грабёж что Ну я тебе
105 I don't know what you have there 105 in the metro
105 я не знаю что у вас там 105 в метро
in Moscow ё sat in
в Москве ё сидел в
Ryazan And what did you work in
Рязани А что ты в
Moscow
Москве
Who did you
работал Кем
work
работал
metropolitan don't Hang out don't Hang out Yes in the
метрополитен не Зависай не Зависай Да в
metro Who did you
метрополитене Кем
work road workers understood paths rashcha understood
работал дорожникам понял пути раща понял
And how will you get that you
А как получишь что ты
someone well
кого-то
Was a little drunk
ну Был немножко пья
crutches that
ком костыли которые прибивают
nail sleepers and all this is straight  at work like there
шпалы и всё это прям на работе типа там
in the subway Yes right in the subway So we went out
в метрополитене Да пря в метро Вот вышли
he started I gave him and everything and immediately on the
он начал я ему как дал и всё и сразу на
lushnya 11 guy for
лушня 11 челе по
death at Yes he died in the hospital he
смерть у Да он в больнице умер он в
died in the hospital not
больнице умер не
right away but it turns out you were drunk at
сразу а получается ты пьяный был на
work not drunk but drunk
работе не пьяный а
drunk yes that is you were drunk
выпивший выпивший да то есть ты выпивший
at work here with this hammer in short magnifying
был на работе вот этим молотком короче
glass zero What year did you do
лупа нул Это в каком году ты
it
его
2022 May month in 2m you amnesty
2022 май месяц в 2м тебя амнисти
Well I'll tell you when no no Listen I'm sorry
Ну скажу тебе когда не не Послушай я
I'm lying to you a little in 2022 In the
тебе извини я тебе вру немножко в 2022 В
month of May I've
мае месяце я
already been half a year from the month of May Count
уже полгода от мая месяца Посчитай
please I just can't count I'm
пожалуйста просто считать не могу я
a little drunk now from the month of May
сейчас немножко выпи от мая месяца
half a year from count Which
полгода от считай В какую
way in the
сторону в
minus I understood
минус понял
that something turns out in the twenty-first
то что то получается в двадцать первом
you kicked him
ты его пнул
yes Well maybe that's how it is even I honestly do
да Ну может быть и так даже я вот честно
n't remember I won't tell you I'm not
вот не помню я тебе не буду я Я теб не
lying to you I'm telling you how it
вру я тебе говорю как
is I understood that is it turns out uh you
есть понял то есть получается ээ ты
screwed up sat for six months in a pretrial detention center you were already
завалил сидел полгода в СИЗО тебе уже
given this sentence Or not Or before the
этот приговор дали Или нет Или до
sentence  amnesty did
приговора амнисти
not give anything sentence I
ничего не дали приговор Я раньше время
jumped off earlier when Putin's
соскочил когда Путинская вот пошла
amnesty came like an amnesty but so that you go to
амнистия типа амнистия но чтоб идёшь на
this you go to war
это идёшь на войну
Yes not to war but to defend the motherland Well
Да не на войну а родину защищать Ну ти
you are in the Wagner PMC yes you went it turns out yes yes
ты в чвк Вагнер да пошл получается да да
yes my friend was there I even
да прихожи мой дуг был я с ним даже за
shook hands with him And listen and why in short
руку здоровался А слушай а почему короче
who killed Prigozhin what do you think Prigozhin no
вот кто убил пригожина как ты считаешь
one killed Prigozhin
Пригожин никто не убил Пригожин в
lives in Belarus that the helicopter was shot down
Белорусии живёт то что вертолёт
Prigozhin lives with his father in the same house
сбили Пригожин с батькой в одном доме
you are more than sure I tell you Do you
живёт тебе больше чем уверен тебе говорю
know such a father Yes
Знаешь такого батьку Да
yes it's not like your expired
да это не то что ваш там просроченный
president there I'm watching a movie now about
президент во я сечас кино смотрю про
yours who fought the occupiers the
ваших которые вот с оккупантами боролись
movie is on now I'll tell you what it's
кино он сейчас идёт сейчас скажу как
called even now wait now I'll take the
называется даже сейчас подожди сейчас
remote control
пульт
prime minister liberation of
премьера освобождение
Donbass Listen and
Донбасса Слушай а
how do I get it right I understand that you
как я правильно получаю понимаю что ты
went to work in Moscow there was drunk
поехал работать в Москву там под выпил
at work and with this sledgehammer which is there
на работе и вот этим кувалдой который
rails  something sleepers in short warm
там рельсы что-то шпал короче варм
which sleepers are nailed with a pin which sleepers are
которы шпалы прибивают штырём которым
nailed with
шпалы прибивает
lunulae I just started to climb onto the
лунулы я просто стал подниматься на
platform he me
платформу он
I don't blow
меня я не дую
and that's it Pony in short some
и вс Поня короче какого-то
passenger yes yes that's right passenger
пассажира да да вот правильно пассажира
I'm not saying
Я не говорю
that in the end it turned out That is you in short
то в концовке оказал То есть ты короче
some passenger with a crowbar he hit the bast shoes
какого-то пассажира ломом он двинул
yes and you didn't
лапти да и ты не сразу
move right away well in this hit the bast shoes in the hospital
двину ну в этом двинул лапти
you spent six months in a pre-trial
в в больни ты полгода отсидел в СИЗО
detention center pre-trial detention center sung even in the zone would be
СИЗО спет даже на зоне бы
in the PMC Wagner and also got money for it Well let it
в чвк Вагнер ещ и бабки за это
be as you
получил Ну пускай будет так как ты
think
думаешь
understood Well I voluntarily signed no one
понял Ну я доброволь подписал мне никто
forced me to go Yes voluntarily signed
не заставлял ити Да добровольно подписал
you voluntarily they told us we're making an amnesty
тебе добровольно сказали делаем амнистию
yes
да
this
этой
life I now have until the end of my life
жизни У меня теперь до конца моей жиз
My children 50% pay for gas light only
Мои дети 50% платить за газ засвет всего
50% I'm a veteran of military operations Okay
50% я ветеран боевых действий Окей
look before the war here's the war in the second
смотри до войны вот война в д втором
year yes you started before the year
году да у вас началась до д вго года
2000 Putin has been the ruler since 2022
Путин с 2000 года 22 года был правитель
What is he to you  did so that you could live
Да что он для тебя сделал чтобы ты жил
well Your children so that they would have to do it this way
хорошо Твои дети чтобы те пришлось
with us first of all I am a
так у нас это самое во-первых я
father of many children I have two sons
многодетный отец у меня два сыночка
sweetheart daughter let the wife be there But I don't
лапочка дочка пускай жена там Но это я
think so now But I am grateful to her
сейчас е считаю Но я ей благодарен то
that she gave birth to her
что она родила своих
children he always helped us first of all Putin
детей он нам всегда помогал во-первых у
always helped us like you Putin helped us
всегда как вам Путин помогал участок нам
Putin personally gave us a plot Please repeat again personally
Путин Ещё раз повтори пожалуста лично
Putin allocated you his land
Путин выделил вам землю свою
Yes the state allocated us land but with Putin's
Да государство нам выделило землю но с
orders Putin personally instructed you to
поручения Путин лично поручил вам
allocate land Well not specifically to us but to
выделить землю Да ну не конкретно нам а
all Russians who have many children whose
всем россиянам которые вот многодет чья
land Whose land was this our Russian
Земля Чья это Земля была наша русская
land in That is to say Tin gave you your own
земля во То есть тин дал вам вашу же
land Yes yes yes everything is exactly like that everything is exactly like that
землю Да да да всё именно так всё именно
gave us our land Well and
так и есть дал нам нашу Землю Ну а вам
why didn't Zelensky give you that Wait
что ж Зеленский так не давал Подожди
wait stop stop I just understand Tepa it
подожди стоп стоп я просто понимаю Тепа
means Putin is great because he gave you a
значит Путин молодец потому что дал вам
piece of your life Okay what else did
кусочек вашей жи Окей что ещё для вас
Putin
Путин
do for you Well he paid us a hundred per month
сделал Ну по сотке нам платил ежемесячно
in hryvnia how much to transfer for TH children
на гривну сколько перевести за ТХ детей
yes x children Yes per hundred is how much per
да х детей Да по сотке это по сколько на
child yes  I say yes, they paid us a hundred for the
ребёнка да я да говорю по сотке нам на
three of us, that's a lot, for the
троих платили что-то сильно много за
youngest they paid us thirty, the older one is
самую младшую нам тридцатку платили
still 25, well, well,
25 ещё там ну ну
practically, wait, 35 and
практи подожди 35 и
25, I'm practically a hundred,
25 я те практически сотка выходила
practically, it won't even come out to
практиче уже даже практически не выйдет
a hundred,
сотка
what are you going to count my money for?
ты что за мной будешь мои деньги считать
Now tell me that you're green. You're cheating.
Вот ты скажи что те зеле Ты обманываешь
You're cheating. It turns out that way. Look. What are
Ты обманываешь получается так смотри А
your salaries there? What are your
какие у вас зарплаты там какие у вас
salaries in
зарплаты в
Ryazan? Well, it depends on where. Well, what. Well, it
Рязани Ну смотря
depends on where you are. Tell me at least an
какие Ну го смотря где ты мне скажи хоть
example. Who works where? What did you work in the
пример Кто где работает что ты работал в
subway? What's your salary?
метрополитене ско тебя Зар
My salary was 150. It was really
у меня было 150 реально было
150,000 in the
150.000 в метрополита
Moscow subway. Yes. And at home in Ryazan, how much would the
Москвы так да А дома в Рязане сколько
salary be, plus the housing was
зарплаты бы и плюс е жильё было
free, super. And in Ryazan, how much would the
бесплатное супер А в Рязани сколько
salary be? Well, in Ryazan, I don't know
зарплаты Ну в Рязани у нас я не знаю
such salaries, I've never seen them. You can get them.
таких зарплаты я ни разу не встречал
If you work from dawn to
можно получать Если будешь От зари до
dawn, there's no market. You can get them
зари это Базара нет сотку можно получать
from dawn.  before
если От зари до
dawn on construction And I do
зари на строительстве А таких я таких
n't know such such positions where there is
должностей не знаю где вот там
someone there somewhere sitting in
кто-нибудь там где-нибудь сидит в
offices Maybe they get
кабинетах Может они и получают по
half a million I'm talking about who the workers get I have a
полмиллиона Я говорю кто работяги
friend who works as a
получают вот у меня друг работает
tiler mason they do everything he
плиточником каменщиком всё делают он
gets a hundred that is 1000 dollars this is
сотку получает то есть 1000 долларов это
his ceiling yes Yes his
его потолок да
ceiling Yes 1000 dollars
Да потолок евошний Да 1000 долларов
his good but look And why do
евошний хорошо а вот смотри И почему в у
Europeans have lice ceilings of 5000 10,000
европейцев е вош потолки 5000 10.000
dollars yes And you don't
долларов да А у вас
know what kind of Europeans you
сся не знают каких европейцев такие
know ceilings Europeans are so
знаешь потолки европейцы там какие
smart Well what do you think
дельные Ну как ты считаешь
Why don't I know
Почему я не знаю
such people they get 6 dollars
таких 6 долларов
And how much do they get
получают А сколько они получают
there yes maximum dollars 700
там да максимум долларов 700
7800 for free Yes market they don't live on
7800 на халяву Да базар не живут на
freebies Where in Europe gets
халяву Где в Европе получает
78 Where in Europe
78 Где в Европе 700-800
gets 700-800 Well that's how much you get yours
получают Ну ты вот сколько получаешь сво
Where in Europe gets 78 700-800
по Где в Европе получает 78 700-800
dollars in
долларов в
Switzerland in Switzerland  get 700-800
Швейцарии в Швейцарии получают 700-800
dollars if not
долларов если не
less Now wait, I'll meditate
меньше Сейчас подожди я помедитируйте
[music]
[музыка]
this is what meditation is called And
это медитация на называется так А
how much is the salary in Switzerland approximately
сколько примерно зарплата в Швейцарии
If
Если
less, well, the salary in Switzerland is probably one and a
меньше ну зарплата в Швейцарии наверное
half thousand
тысячи полторы
maximum, so You said less than
максимум так Ты же говорил меньше
Well, your brother There it turns out
Ну ваш брат Там получается
only Listen, how do the Swiss survive
только Слушай
with such a meager
а как швейцарцы выживают с такой нищей
salary
зарплаты
Well, yours, what do they call it, that's what they
Ну Ваши как как называет так и называют
call it Well, tell me, how do the Swiss survive with such a meager salary, they call it I'm asking you how the
называют Я же тебя спрашиваю как
Swiss survive with
швейцарцы выживают с такой
such a salary I'm telling you what they call it What else can they call it, how do they survive I'm asking you do you know I see your IQ level is growing before my eyes No, I'll ask you a question like this right now How do you survive there with such a
вопрос задам Как вы там выживает с такой
salary Listen, tell me one thing In which
зарплатой Слушай скажи мне одно В каких
countries have you been besides
странах ты был кроме
Russia in countries there were no in cities
России в странах не было в городах был
I'm not a refugee I'm not running anywhere
Я же не беженец я же не бегу никуда
your
своей
Rhone could you, for example,
Роны ты мог например там в Турцию
go on vacation to Turkey and not in Turkey was
поехать на отдых а не в Турции был
Turkey I don't think Turkey is where
Турции Я не считаю Турция что это где
besides Turkey
кроме Турции
was I knew their language I don't know
был в Турции язна был ихний язык не знаю
theirs I don't know at all  I was in
их Я вообще знани я был в
Turkey I would have
Турции бы
even been
отеле даже был
in a
м в
two-zone hotel where are you like that in Turkey I
двухзонный отель где ты такой в Турции
found
нашёл
a two-zone hotel they said it was a five-star
двухзонному сказали пяти звёздочный но
hotel but there were no five stars there was a buffet yes you could have
там не было пяти звёзд шведский стол был
I was there every day
да там можно было я там вот каждый день
I'll tell you honestly every day I was Jan
Я честно скажу каждый день был Ян В
My friend knows what city I was in in Turkey My first one
регион знает мне подруга Моя первая
brought me everything I paid for I'm a freeloader Well
привезла мне всё оплатил я халявщик Ну
there's Antalya Alanya where is it Sorry
там Анталия Алания мер где Извини
I don't know I won't lie where I've
я не знаю Врать не буду где я
been if you know all the countries their cities
был если ты все страны знае их города
tell me where I've been
скажи ты где я был
15 minutes walk the sea was visible right from the
15 минут ходьбы море было видно прямо с
balcony 15 minutes walk to the sea in Turkey
балкона 15 минут ходьбы до моря в Турции
Well it's a good
Ну хороший
hotel 15 minutes a kilometer Well I say 15 from
отель 15 минут километр Ну я говорю 15
the balcony you can see the
балкона видно
sea
море
Cool Well my ex-girlfriend
Прикольно Ну меня моя бывшая подружка
took me there it was expensive
вози дорого
When was 2007 2006 2007
обошлось Когда было 2007 2006 2007 год
but she says it cost about fifty somewhere
но она говорит около полтинника где-то
2006 is sometime 19 years
обошлось 2006 - это когда-то 19 лет
ago Yes that's how it was I was still 18
назад Да так и было мне ещё было 18
years old and the girl
лет а девчонке
and the girls  18 years old nano mine was a year old
и девчонки 18 лет нано моя на годка была
And what did she decide to
А что она решила так тебя
take you like that again And what did she decide to take you
свозить ещё раз А что она решила тебя
track take why did she decide to go
отследить свозить почему она тебя решила
to Turkey Well we loved each other We
в Турцию Ну любили мы друг друга Мы 7
dated for 7 years before that itself that's the
лет встречались до этого само вот с
age we dated She
такого вот возраста встречались Она
was from Moscow I was from Ryazan I didn't want to go to
москвичка была я рязанец я не хотел в
Moscow that's why for 7 years you
Москву поэтому по 7 лет это вы с 11 лет
dated since you were 11 yes Elina in Moscow VR
встречались да елина в Москве ВР
we met with her all the time Pony she had a
мы с ней постоянно встречались Поня у
dacha in the Ryazan region got it
неё дача была в Рязанской области понял
And listen and here's a question Like did you
А слушай а такой вопрос Типа вы поездом
go by train from Moscow or from Ryazan to Turkey
ехали из Москвы или из Рязани в Турцию
we flew from Moscow by plane how long was the
мы улетали из Москвы на самолёте сколько
flight 4
летели 4
hours to which airport did you arrive in the
часа в какой аэродром прилетели в
city I'm telling you honestly I don't
город вот я тебе честно говорю я вот не
remember I swear you're going to tell me now that
помню вот клянусь ты вот сейчас скажешь
you're lying I honestly don't remember I
то что те вру я вот честно не помню я то
flew away
что улетал
already ugh I went in for the first time she had
уже фю зашёл Я первый раз зашла она-то
already flown before that she was from a good family
уже летала до этого она с хорошей семьи
not with one like
не с такой как
me she you know such fr everything she knows me
я она знаете такой фр всё знает она меня
I started there I took a sip took a sip
завела я там глотнул
I fell asleep and woke up already on the
глотнул я уснул а проснулся уже на
spot and after that
месте и после этого не возила
she didn’t take you anywhere again after that No
да ещё раз после этого она тебя никуда
no
не возила Да нет
why did you fly to Adler again
почему ещё в Адлер
Pony interesting question do you consider
Поня интересный вопрос считаешь ли ты
yourself maybe yes a little I think
себя может быть да чуть считаю может
maybe a little I
быть чуть-чуть
think unexpectedly I just didn’t expect such a thing by No well
считаю неожиданно я прям не ожидал
think How many
считаю На сколько
percent Well probably 45 percent
процентов Ну процентов наверное на 45
so it’s almost
так это почти на
half well no more than
половину ну не больше чем
you cool 45% is a pretty good
ты прикольно 45% довольно хороший
indicator of your IQ okay I’ll run 200
показатель твоего IQ ладно побежал я 200
Come on run
Давай бежи
this is
это
brutal Let’s like a squeak comment a letter to y
жесть Давайте лайк писка комент пись на
Telegram right now axis VN
й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scargi ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарги ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don’t show to people at times I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational connection is
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video still tezhe tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж е цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
letter a
пись а